<content id="832"><contentSection id="1">
				<title>
					Creature Power
				</title>
				<navigationLabel>
					Guinea Fowl Power!
				</navigationLabel>
				<contentItems>
					<contentItem id="126">
						<title>
							
						</title>
						<text>
							This guinea fowl has a round body, small head, short legs, and long toes. Guinea fowl can have bright blue or red patches of skin and grey-black body plumage dotted with white flecks. Guinea fowl can fly in short bursts, but usually walk or run to get around.
						</text>
						<order>
							0
						</order>
						<mediaItem id="165">
							<mediaType>image</mediaType>
							<uri>
								/wildkratts/media/creaturepedia/41/Guinea fowl main.png
							</uri>
						</mediaItem>
					</contentItem>
				</contentItems>
			</contentSection><contentSection id="2">
				<title>
					Food and Health
				</title>
				<navigationLabel>
					Food and Health
				</navigationLabel>
				<contentItems>
					<contentItem id="126">
						<title>
							
						</title>
						<text>
							Guinea fowl spend the day feeding on the ground, mostly in the early morning and early evening. They eat many kinds of foods including seeds, bulbs, berries and flowers as well as grasshoppers, termites, snails and other small invertebrates.  The birds sometimes follow monkey troops gathering up any fallen fruit the primates drop.
						</text>
						<order>
							0
						</order>
						<mediaItem id="165">
							<mediaType>image</mediaType>
							<uri>
								/wildkratts/media/creaturepedia/41/Guinea fowl group.png
							</uri>
						</mediaItem>
					</contentItem>
				</contentItems>
			</contentSection><contentSection id="3">
				<title>
					Home Base
				</title>
				<navigationLabel>
					Home Base
				</navigationLabel>
				<contentItems>
					<contentItem id="126">
						<title>
							
						</title>
						<text>
							Guinea fowl live in Africa, south of the Sahara Desert, and can be found within grasslands with small shrubs, arid or moist wooded savannas, forests, or dense thickets.
						</text>
						<order>
							0
						</order>
						<mediaItem id="165">
							<mediaType>image</mediaType>
							<uri>
								/wildkratts/media/creaturepedia/41/Guinea fowl home base.png
							</uri>
						</mediaItem>
					</contentItem>
				</contentItems>
			</contentSection><contentSection id="4">
				<title>
					Danger Alert
				</title>
				<navigationLabel>
					Danger Alert
				</navigationLabel>
				<contentItems>
					<contentItem id="126">
						<title>
							
						</title>
						<text>
							Guinea fowl mostly live in groups. Some species gather in large flocks of up to 200 birds. Working together, they squawk and flap their wings to confuse predators. When threatened, guinea fowl fly in short bursts or run into the bushes to escape. At night, guinea fowl take to the trees for protection.
						</text>
						<order>
							0
						</order>
						<mediaItem id="165">
							<mediaType>image</mediaType>
							<uri>
								/wildkratts/media/creaturepedia/41/Guinea fowl close up.png
							</uri>
						</mediaItem>
					</contentItem>
				</contentItems>
			</contentSection><contentSection id="5">
				<title>
					Livin' Creature Style
				</title>
				<navigationLabel>
					Livin' Guinea Fowl Style!
				</navigationLabel>
				<contentItems>
					<contentItem id="126">
						<title>
							
						</title>
						<text>
							Guinea fowl parents pair up in the breeding season and the female guinea fowl lays a nest of 7 to 20 eggs that she incubates for about 28 days. The male guinea fowl doesn't help incubate, but he stands guard, keeping the female and incubating chicks safe.
						</text>
						<order>
							0
						</order>
						<mediaItem id="165">
							<mediaType>image</mediaType>
							<uri>
								/wildkratts/media/creaturepedia/41/Guinea fowl creature power.png
							</uri>
						</mediaItem>
					</contentItem>
				</contentItems>
			</contentSection></content>